<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Recipe</string>
    <string name="btn">Up</string>
    <string name="d1">Buffalo Chicken Dip</string>
    <string name="d2">Mini Caramel Rolls</string>
    <string name="d3">Three-Bean Baked Beans</string>
    <string name="d4">Pepper Poppers</string>
    <string name="d5">sour Cream Chip Muffins</string>
    <string name="d6">Onion Beef Au Jus</string>
    <string name="t1">This is the best buffalo chicken dip recipe! Whenever I bring it to a tailgate or potluck, everyone asks for the recipe.</string>
    <string name="t2">Here\'s the perfect warm treat for pajama-clad family mornings. These ooey-gooey baked rolls come together in moments—thanks to a tube of refrigerated crescent rolls—and disappear just as quickly.</string>
    <string name="t3">I got this recipe from an aunt and made a couple of changes to suit our tastes. With ground beef and bacon mixed in, these satisfying beans are a big hit at backyard barbecues and church picnics. I\'m always asked to bring my special beans.</string>
    <string name="t4">These creamy stuffed jalapenos have some bite. They may be the most popular treats I make! My husband is always hinting that I should make a batch.</string>
    <string name="t5">Take one bite and you\'ll see why I think these rich, tender muffins are the best I\'ve ever tasted. Mint chocolate chips make them a big hit with my family and friends.</string>
    <string name="t6">Garlic, onions, soy sauce and onion soup mix flavor the tender beef in these savory hot sandwiches served with a tasty, rich broth for dipping. The seasoned beef makes delicious cold sandwiches, too.</string>
    <string name="r1">"1 package (8 ounces) cream cheese, softened 1 cup cooked chicken breast 1/2 cup Buffalo wing sauce 1/2 cup ranch or blue cheese salad dressing 2 cups shredded Colby-Monterey Jack cheese French bread baguette slices, celery ribs or tortilla chips. \\n  Preheat oven to 350°. Spread cream cheese into an ungreased shallow 1-qt. baking dish. Layer with chicken, wing sauce and salad dressing. Sprinkle with cheese. Bake, uncovered, 20-25 minutes or until cheese is melted. Serve with baguette slices. "</string>
    <string name="r2">1/3 cup packed brown sugar 1/3 cup butter, cubed 2 tablespoons light corn syrup 1-1/2 teaspoons 2% milk 1 tube (8 ounces) refrigerated crescent rolls 2 teaspoons sugar 1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon. Preheat oven to 375°. In a small saucepan, combine brown sugar, butter, corn syrup and milk; cook and stir over medium heat until blended. Pour into a greased 9-in. pie plate. Separate crescent dough into 4 rectangles; gently press perforations to seal. In a small bowl, mix sugar and cinnamon.</string>
    <string name="r3"> pork and beans, undrained 1 can (16 ounces) butter beans, rinsed and drained 1 can (16 ounces) kidney beans, rinsed and drained. Preheat oven to 350°. In a large skillet, cook and crumble beef with bacon and onion over medium heat until beef is no longer pink; drain. Stir in sugars, ketchup, barbecue sauce, molasses, mustard, chili powder and salt until blended. Stir in beans. Transfer to a greased 2-1/2-qt. baking dish. Bake, covered, until beans reach desired thickness, about 1 hour. </string>
    <string name="r4">1/4 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon garlic powder 1/4 teaspoon chili powder 1 pound fresh jalapenos, halved lengthwise and seeded 1/2 cup dry bread crumbs . In a large bowl, combine the cheeses, bacon and seasonings; mix well. Spoon about 2 tablespoonfuls into each pepper half. Roll in bread crumbs. Place in a greased 15x10x1-in. baking pan. Bake, uncovered, at 325° for 15 minutes for spicy flavor, 25 minutes for medium and 35 minutes for mild. Serve with sour cream, dip or dressing.</string>
    <string name="r5">1 large egg 1 cup sour cream 5 tablespoons butter, melted 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 3/4 cup mint or semisweet chocolate chips. In a large bowl, combine the flour, sugar, baking powder, baking soda and salt. Combine the egg, sour cream, butter and vanilla. Stir into dry ingredients just until moistened. Fold in chocolate chips. Fill greased or paper-lined muffin cups three-fourths full. Bake at 350° for 18-20 minutes or until a toothpick inserted in the center comes out clean. Cool for 5 minutes before removing from pan to a wire rack.</string>
    <string name="r6">5 cups water 1/2 cup reduced-sodium soy sauce 1 envelope onion soup mix 1 garlic clove, minced 1 teaspoon browning sauce, optional 1 loaf (1 pound) French bread . In a Dutch oven over medium-high heat, brown roast on all sides in oil; drain. In a large skillet, saute onions in 2 tablespoons of butter until tender. Add the water, soy sauce, soup mix, garlic and, if desired, browning sauce. Pour over roast. Cover and bake at 325° for 2-1/2 hours or until meat is tender. </string>
    <string name="splash">Recipe app</string>
</resources>